#### Contact

ashworld12136@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ashutosh-kushwah-1600a21a8 (LinkedIn)

## Top Skills

Artificial Intelligence (AI)
Python (Programming Language)
C++

### Languages

Hindi (Native or Bilingual)
English (Professional Working)

### Certifications

Cryptocurrency and Blockchain Artificial Intelligence

# **ASHUTOSH KUSHWAH**

Data Science Enthusiast | Market Research Raipur

## Summary

Precocious undergrad ready to accept increasingly complex challenges associated with maintaining and exploiting growing data stores. Driven to expand experience through hands-on training and guided participation in effective data science tasks. Ready to immediately contribute beneficial input to the employers. Attentive and offering sharp time management, organizational and assistance skills. Personable individual willing to work hard and take on any task.

# Experience

Codepth
Data Science Intern
July 2020 - Present (2 months)
Bhubaneshwar, Orissa, India

Advertere: The Marketing Society Market Research Associate July 2020 - Present (2 months) New Delhi, Delhi, India

## Education

Kalinga Institute of Industrial Technology, Bhubaneswar Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Computer Science · (2018 - 2022)

Sainik School Ambikapur (2010 - 2017)

Sacred Heart Senior Secondary School - India · (2003 - 2009)